cugiz.com 2012-06-14

# Cugiz: Privacy Policy

http://www.cugiz.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site.

 _Third Party Advertising_

We use Google AdSense and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

 _Third Party Cookies_

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser.

 _Personal Information_

We do not request any personal information or collect any information that personally identifies you or allows you to be personally contacted. Since we do not collect any personal information on this Web site, we do not share any personal information with any third parties nor do we use any personal information for any purposes.

 _External Links_

This site contains links to other sites. http://www.cugiz.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

 _Contacting the Web Site_

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact contact@cugiz.com

We have no © on some of these images/videos. If you find your image/video which is copyrighted mail us to [contact@cugiz.com] we’ll remove them within the next 24hrs
